{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"6.84/9",
			"answer":"6.84/9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"6.4/0.002",
			"answer":"6.4/0.002",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"9.57/3",
			"answer":"9.57/3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"58.8/6",
			"answer":"58.8/6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"880/0.5",
			"answer":"880/0.5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"630/3",
			"answer":"630/3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7.44/0.3",
			"answer":"7.44/0.3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"80.8/0.02",
			"answer":"80.8/0.02",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.342/0.6",
			"answer":"0.342/0.6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"940/0.05",
			"answer":"940/0.05",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	
	]
}